klientboost.com 2014-10-25

# Privacy Policy

By working with and using KlientBoost.com, you agree to the collection and use of your information as stated in this policy. If any changes are made to our privacy policy we will notify you via e-mail and update it on this page as well.

### **Summary**

  * We will never give, sell, rent or borrow your information to anyone.
  * We will never spam you.
  * We will never work with another client who is your direct geographic competitor.
  * We will never have direct access to your payment methods without your consent.

### **How we treat your information**

**  
We will never give, sell, rent or borrow your information to anyone.**  
– We respect your privacy and your trust. We will therefore never give, sell, rent or borrow your information to anyone without your express permission.

**We will never spam you.  
**\- We do send updates about your account, regular correspondence between you and your klient account manager, blog postings, news about KlientBoost, and newsletters. You do have the ability to unsubscribe at any time.

**We will never work with another client who is your direct geographic competitor.  
**\- Conflict of interest is no fun. That’s why we promise to never directly work with a competitor of yours who is of direct competition without your express permission.

**We will never have direct access to your payment methods without your consent.**  
– When signing up for our services, we do require that you sign up for a month to month billing pattern that automatically deducts payments from your method of payment. We will encrypt your payment information so no one can for example see your 16 digit card number you have supplied. We will not be able to go in and charge more than you’ve specified without your consent.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the service requested.

### **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you fill out the form on our site and when asking you questions about your business and making the appropriate decisions when creating strategies in regards to your marketing efforts.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number or credit card information.

**Personal:** name, e-mail addresses, phone numbers.  
**Transactions:** Bills and payments.

### **How do we protect your information?**

We implement an SSL (secure socket layer) that protects your payment information.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes, but unfortunately not the delicious kind. Cookies, sometimes known as pixels, are small files that a site transfers to your computer that can recognize your browser and remember certain information.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

You can always delete or opt-out of this cookie/pixel experience by clearing your browser cookies.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We will therefore not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. Just like we mentioned earlier.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
**We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only  
**This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms of Service  
**Please visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website and services.  
Simply click on “terms” on the sign up form.

**Your Consent  
**By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy  
**Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 02/18/2013

### **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

www.klientboost.com  
409 Utica Avenue, Suite 3  
Huntington Beach, California 92647  
USA  
hello@klientboost.com  
1-800-328-6186
